Guide to the Denise Levertov Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. Correspondence
  - a. Incoming
    - Creeley, Robert [Letters to Mitchell Goodman], 1954 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Creeley, Robert [Letters to Mitchell Goodman, undated], 1951 - 1953 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Creeley, Robert, c. 1949 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1950 - 1951 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1951 Jan. - Feb. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1951 Mar. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1951 Apr. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1951 Aug. - Oct. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1951 Nov. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Creeley, Robert, c. 1951 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1954 Jan. - July (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1954 Aug. - Dec. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1967 - 1969 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1971 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1980 - 1984 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Creeley, Robert, MSS (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Creeley, Robert [letter of recommendation], 1989 - 1997, 1 ANS, 3 TLS (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Creins, Martha, 1993, 2 TLS (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Crelan - Cross B. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Crews, Judson, 1992, 1 TLS (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Cross, Nick, 1960 - 1975, MSS (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Crossley, Robert [University of Massachusetts], 1996 Nov., 1 TLS (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Crouch, Terrill (1970 - 1988) - Crouteau, David (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Crowder, Ashby Bland, 1980 - 1986 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Crowder, Ashby Band, 1986, 1 ANS, 1 TLS [Bernard Oldsey], 1 MNS (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Crowley, Paul SJ, 1993 May, 1 TLS (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Crown, Bonnie, 1963 - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Crown, Bonnie, 1965 - 1968 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Crozier, Andrew, 1964 - 1967 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Cruz, Casimira, 1960 - 1962 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Csikszentmihalya, Mihaly [University of Chicago], 1993 Nov., 1 TLS (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Cuddihy, Michael, n.d., TLS (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Cuddily - Cullom (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Cumbie - Cumming, P. (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Cumming, Roxanne, M.D., 1970 -1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Cumming, Roxanne, 1977 - 1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cumming, Roxanne, 1992 - 1996, 2 ANS (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Cummings - Currey (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Cummins, James, 1979 Apr., 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Cundeo, Andrew, 1995, 1 TLS, 1 C.V. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Cunneen, Joseph, n.d., 1 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cunneen, Sally, 1992 Apr., 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Curry, David (1967 - 1971) - Curry, Leon (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Curtis, Margaret Alice Jones (Mickey), n.d.; 1968 - 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Curtis, Margaret Alice Jones (Mickey), 1973 - 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Curtis, Margaret Alice Jones (Mickey), 1979 - 1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Curtis, Margaret Alice Jones (Mickey), 1985 - 1986 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Curtis, Margaret Alice Jones (Mickey), 1987 - 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Curtis, Tony, 1976 - 1984, MSS (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Cushman, Dan, n.d., 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Cutler, Bess - Cutler E. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Cutler, Virginia Tyler, 1993 Feb., 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Cutter, William, n.d., 1 ALS (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - D misc. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Dabney, Janice, 1982, MSS (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - D'Agostino - Dana, Ri (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Dajani, Virginia, 1994 Apr., 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Dana, Robert, MSS (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Daly, Rev. Padraig J., 1993 - 1997, 2 ALS, 1 PC (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Dana, Robert, 1970 - 1984, MSS (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Dana, Robert, 1995 Oct., 2 TLS (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Danforth, E. Victoria, 1976, MSS (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Daniel, John, c. 1982 - c. 1984, TMs MSS (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Daniel, John, 1985 - 1988, TMs (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Daniel, John, 1988 - 1990, 19 TLS, 8 ALS, 5 MNS (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Daniel, R. - Daniels, J. (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Daniels, Kate, 1983 - 1988 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Daniels - Dammers (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Damon, Maria, 1982 - 1987 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - [Dardess] - David (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - d'Aurelle, Claire [Paupieres de Terre], 1938, 1 ALS (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Davidon, Ann, 1964 - 1978, MSS (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Davidson, Lise, 1983 - 1985, MSS (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Davidson, Lise, 1985, MSS ("Soon My Branch will Break") (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Davidson, Michael, 1989 June - July, 1 TLS, 1 PC (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Davie, D. - Davison, P. (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Davis, Judy, 1994, 1 ANS (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Davis, Marty, 1993 Nov., 1 ANS (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Davis - Putter Scholarship Fund, 1989, 1 TLS (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Davis, Tim, n.d., 1 MNS - ANS (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Davis, Todd [Goshen College], 1997, 2 TLS (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Dawes, Christopher, 1969 - 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Dawson, Chester, 1973 - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Dawson - Day (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Day, John, 1973 - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Dean, Harold, 1971 - 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Dean, Tom, 1997 Sept., 1 ALS (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Deane, Herbie Scott (Akil), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Deane, John F., 1989 - 1997, 17 ANS, 6 ALS, 4 MNS (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Deanna, Grace, 1958 - 1986 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Dear, John, 1993 - 1996, 2 ALS, 1 TLS, 1 PC (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - De Bellis - Dees (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Deffry, Frank M., 1963 - 1966, MSS (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Deffry, Frank M., 1967 - c. 1969, MSS (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - de Graaf, John, 1986, MSS (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - De Gruson - De Ialla (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - de LaMarc, W. (1946) - Delbridge, Catherine (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - De Lalla, Beatrice, 1989 Dec., 1 ALS (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - de la Marc, Walter, 1947 July 14, TLS (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - DeLoach, Allen, 1970, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Delgado, Ana Maria (1979 - 1981) (TMs) - Delgado, Enrique (1996) (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Del Giudice, Stephen, 1976 - 1982, MSS (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Dellums - Del Vento (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Dema - Demming, A. (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Deming, Barbara, 1967 - 1972 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Deming, Barbara, 1972 - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Deming, Richard [plumtree], 1994 Apr., 1 PC (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Dempsey - DeNitte (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Dennis, Rodney [curator, Houghton Library, Harvard University], 1963 - 1988, MSS (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Dennison, George, 1963 - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Denton, Enid, 1979 - 1980 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - DePaoli, Mike, 1993 - 1997, 2 TLS, 2 ANS (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - De Porte, Michael, 1995, 2 TLS (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - de Rauchewitz, Mary, 1960 - 1966 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - de Rauchewitz, Mary, 1967 - 1980 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - de Rauchewitz, Sizzo, 1963 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - de Rauchewitz, Walter, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Deren, Jane, 1970 - 1975, TMs (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Dern - De Schweinitz, Elizabeth, 1977 - 1988 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - De Schweinitz, Alex, 1989 - 1992, 2 AMS, 8 TLS, 14 TM, 14 ALS (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - De Schweinitz, Alex, 1993 - 1995, 1 AM, 17 TM, 6 TMS, 6 ANS, 13 ALS (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - De Schweinitz, Alex, 1989 - 1995, 3 ALS, 1 TLS, 3 ANS (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - De Schweinitz, Alex, 1965 - 1976 Sept. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1976 - 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1978, MSS (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1979 - 1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1982 - 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1985 - 1987, MSS (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - De Schweinitz, George, 1989, 2 ALS (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Destiny, Diane - DeHelbach, Cynthia (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Deutch, Babette - Deutch, Denise (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Deutch, Richard, n.d.; 1962 - 1963, TMs (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Deutch, Richard, 1964 - 1976, TMs (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Dever, Mary, 1956 - 1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Devi, Dorothy, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1967 - 1973 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1974 - 1983, MSS (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1984 - 1988, TMs (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1989 - 1997, 2 TLS, 1 PC, 6 ALS, 2 ANS, 3 TL (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1982 - 1983, TMs (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - DeVinck, Catherine, 1985 - 1987, TMs (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Devlin, Jim, c. 1975, TMs (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Dewar, Heather, 1993, 1 ALS (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Dewey, Anne, 1995 - 1997, 1 ALS, 1 TLS, 1 PC (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - DeWitt, Susan V., n.d.; 1996, 2 TLS, 1 ACS, TM (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Dia Art Foundation, 1990 Mar., 1 TLS (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - DIA Center for the Arts [Brighde__], 1993, 1 ANS (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Diaz, Nydia (and Leo), 1986 - 1987 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Dibble, Brian, 1972, TMs (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Dickey, James, 1964 - 1965 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Dickinson, Sharleen [student], 1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Diel, Paul, 1974 - 1975, TMs (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Diener - Diggory (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Digges, Deborah, 1992 Apr., TLS (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Dike, Donald (and son, Gregor Dike), 1961 - 1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - DiLanian, Gerard, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Dillon - Diorio (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Dineen, James, M.D., 1989, 1 TLS (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - di Piero, Simone, 1986 - 1988, TMs (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - di Piero, W. S., 1991 - 1997, 3 TNS, 2 TLS, 1 PC (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Di Prima, Diane, 1966 - 1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Dirlam, Barbara, 1970 - 1976, TMsS (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Divok, Mario, n.d., 1 ALS (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Djerassi, Carl, 1983, TMsS (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Doane - Dobson, Parrish (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Dobkin, Bonnie [McDougal Littell / Houghton Mifflin, 1996, 2 TLS (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Dobson, Rosemary, 1981 - 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Dockery, Anne, c. 1973 - 1986, TMs (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Dockery, Anne, 1982 Dec. 17, 1 ALS (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Dodd, Christopher, 1986, [politician] (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation, n.d., 1 ANS (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Doerr, Harriet, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Dolan, Barbara, c. 1987 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Dolci Danilo "Rome", c. 1983, MSS - "From Mouth to Mouth" (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Dollinger - Dolloff (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Damin, Hilde, c. 1965 - 1971, MSS (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Donaldson, Sue, 1996, 1 TLS (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Donahoe - Donahue (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Donelan, Stephen, 1969 - 1972, MSS (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Doniachi, Sara, 1984 - 1987, MSS (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Donohue, Sheila, 1993 Dec., 1 TLS (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Donovan - Donovan-Yarde (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Doolittle, Hilda, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Doress, Irvin Yitzhakq, 1975, TMs (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Dorfman, Ariel, 1982 - 1987 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Dorfman, Ellie, n.d.; 1961 - 1968 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Dorfman, Ellie, 1968 - 1972, MSS (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Dorgan, Theo [Poetry Ireland / Eigse Eireann], 1995, 1 ALS (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Dorn, Alfred, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1947 - 1956, MSS (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1956 - 1958, MSs (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Dorn, Edward, c. 1959 - 1962, MSS (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Dorn, Edward, 1961 - 1962 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Dorn, Helene, 1959 - 1961 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Dorney, Tom, 1968 - 1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Dorney, Tom, 1994 - 1997, ALS, ANS (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Dorset, Gerald - Dougall, Lucy (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Doty, Gene Warren [ne Warren, Francis Eugene, 1991, 1TLS + 2 MNS (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Dougherty, Edward A. - Douskey, Franz, 1975 - c. 1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Dougherty, Edward, 1990 - 1992, 3 ALS, 1 MNs (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Dowd - Downing (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Dozier, Brent, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Dozier, Brent, 1987, MSS "Poems from War and Peace" (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Drake, Elizabeth - Duboff, Judith (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Drake, Sandra, n.d., 1 ANS (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Drucker, Eugene, 1990, 1 ANS (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Dube, Janet, 1995 Dec., 1 TLS (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Dubroff, Susanne, 1975 - 1978, MSS (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Dubroff, Susanne, 1978, MSS (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Dubroff, Susanne, 1979 - 1983 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Dubroff, Susanne, 1995 - 1997, 4 ALS, 1 TLS, 3 TMS, 13 TM, 1 ANS (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Dubus, Andre, 1997, 1 PC (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Duckworth, William, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Duddy, T. (1967 - 1982) - Dufault (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Dukakis, Michael S., 1977, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Dunbar, Judy, n.d.; 1978 - 1982 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Dunbar, Judy, 1983 - 1985 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Dunbar, Judy, 1986 - 1988 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Dunbar, Judy, 1987 - 1997, 22 ALS, 4 ANS, 7 PC (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Dunkary - [Dunsmair] (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - duPlessis, Nancy - duPlessis, Rachel (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blan, 1989, [Including transcription of correspondence from George Oppen to Denise Levertov, 1963 Feb. - Apr. housed at UCSD] (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - DuPre - Durham (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - DuPre, Robyn, 1992, 1 TLS (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Durand, Lou Oma, 1996 and n.d., 1 TLS, 54 ALS, 9 ALS, 3 PC (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Durkin, Arlene, 1981 - 1983 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Durkin, Sister Mary Brian, c. 1968 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Duryee, Carolyn, 1993 Aug., 1 ANS (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Dusenbery, Gail, 1967 - 1970 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Duva - Dwyer (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Dymm, David (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1971 Oct. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Duncan, Robert, n.d., TMS - "Three Songs of the Bard Orpheus" (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Duncan, Robert, TMS - Autobiographical Sketch (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1947, Galley Proof, "Heavenly City, Earthly City," 4 pp. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1953, TMsS, "Passages from a Notebook," with comments by R.D. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Duncan, Robert, c. 1953, TMs, "Faust Foutu, Act I" (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Duncan, Robert, c. 1956, TMs, "Medea at Kochis The Maiden Head" Letter from R.D. to D.L. included (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1958, TMs, from Letters (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1960, TMs - from "The Opening of the Field"; MSs - "Yes, as a Look Springs to its Face" (vr.1) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1960, TMs - from "The Opening of the Field"; MSs - "Yes, as a Look Springs to its Face" (vr.1) (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1956 - 1972, TMs, AMs, Misc. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Duncan, Robert, TMs copy, "Adam's Way" (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1964, TMs - from Roots and Branches (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1959 - 1960, TMs - "Roots and Branches" from Roots and Branches, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1964, TMs - "Nel Mezzo DelCammin Di Nostra Vita," "O Be a Nurse to Me and Tell Me Once Again" from Roots and Branches (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1968, TMs - "Paggages" from Bending the Bow (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1968, TMs - "Paggages" from Bending the Bow (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1968, TMs - from Bending the Bow (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1969, TMs - "The Green Lady" from Derivatives (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1970, TMs - "The Feast Passages," from Tribunal Passages (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1971, TMs and printed material - "A Seventeenth Century Suite (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1960s, Photographs of R. Duncan and prints by Jess Collins (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1950 - 1953, TSS, "A Book of Resemblances; Poems 1950 - 1953" (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1956 - 1959, TSS, "The Opening of the Field, Poems 1956 - 1959" (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Duncan, Robert, Drafts / copies of letters from Levertov to Duncan (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Duncan, Robert, c. 1958 - 1964, undated correspondence (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1957 Jan - 1957 Oct. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1957 Nov. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1958 Jan. - June (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1958 July - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1959 Jan. - June (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1959 July - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1960 Jan. - Mar. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1960 Apr. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1961 Jan. - June (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1961 July - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1962 Jan. - May (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1962 Jun. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1963 Jan. - Apr. (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1963 May - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1964 Jan. - July (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1964 Aug. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1965 Jan. - June (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1965 July - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1966 Jan. - July (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1966 Aug. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1967 Jan. - June (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1967 July - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1968 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Duncan, Robert, 1969 Jan. - Dec. (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - E., David, 1992 Sept. 5 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - [Eahlen], Don - Eaton, Shirley (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Easley, Anne, [includes articles about Page Smith] (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Eastburn, Chris, 1996 Jan., 1 TLS (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Eaton, Mark R., 1993, 1 ALS (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Eberhart, Betty, 1963 - 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1958 - 1967, TMs (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Eberly, David, n.d.; 1973 - c. 1976, MSS (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Eberman, Willis - Eby, Phyllis (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Ebrahimian, Babu K., 1995 Apr., 1 ALS (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Eckman, Frederick, 1954 - 1964, 1 ALS (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Eddy, Don (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Edelman, Elaine, n.d.; 1970 - 1977 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Edelman, Elaine, 1980 - 1987 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Edelman, Elaine, 1991 - 1995, 1 ALS, 1 PC (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Edelman, Olivia, 1974 - 1985 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Edelman, Olivia, 1992 - 1997, 1 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Edelman, Richard, n.d.; 1973 - 1974 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Edelman, Richard, 1975 - 1977 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Edelman, Richard, 1979 - 1983 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Edelman, Richard, 1984 - 1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Edelman, Richard, 1995 - 1997, 24 TLS (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Edelman, Richard W., 1994 Nov. 29 RESTRICTED (Box 32, Folder 23.1)
    - Edelman, Robert (1974) - Edershiem, Steve (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Edemariam, Aida [Harper's Magazine], 1997 Nov., 1 TLS (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Edmonds, Trevor, 1971 - 1986 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Edson, Russell, 1961 - 1964 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Edwards, Bruce - Edwards, Susan (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Egan, Eileen, n.d.; 1962 - 1978 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Egan, Eileen, 1979 - 1988 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Egan, Eileen, 1989 - 1997, 6 ALS, 5 ANS (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Eggly, Susan and Joeseph, 1981 - 1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Ehrhardt, W.D., 1984 - 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Ehrig, Greta, 1995 Nov., 1 TLS (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Ehrman, Sally (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Eide, Asbjorn, n.d., 2 fragments (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1955 - 1957, TMs (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Eigner, Larry [Lawrence?], 1958, TMs (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1959 +, TMs (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1960 - 1963, TMs (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1968 - 1972, TMs (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Eigner, Larry, n.d. (c. 1957 - 1960), TMs (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Eigner, Larry, n.d.; c. 1957 - 1960, TMs - with notes by Levertov (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Eigner, Larry, n.d.; c. 1957 - 1960, TMs (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Eigner, Larry, n.d.; c. 1957 - 1960, TMs (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1983 - 1987, TMs (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Einhorn, Ira, c. 1966 - 1967 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Eisen, Christine, 1994 Mar., 1 TLS + 1 MNS (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Eisenberg, Susan, c. 1968 - 1980, TMs (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Eisenberg, Susan, 1983 - 1988, TMs (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Eisenberg, Susan, c. 1988, TMs (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Eisenberg, Susan, [acidic material] (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Eisneberg, Susan, 1989 - 1996, 3 TLS, 1 ALS, 4 MNS (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Eisenhood, Beth, 1995 - 1997, 12 ALS, 4 PC (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Eisenstadt, Bob and Margie, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Eisner, David, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Ekner, Reidar, 1960 - 1970, TMs (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Ekner, Reidar, 1980 - 1986, TMs (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Ekner, Reidar, n.d., TMs (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Ekner, Reidar and Eldrid Lunden, 1994 Dec., TNs (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Elbow, Peter - Elgin, Larry (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Elias, Victor, n.d.; 1971 - 1977, TMs (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Elias, Victor, 1981, TMs (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Eliot, T.S., 1958 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Elledge, Scott - Elkin, Rachel (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ellingham, Lewis, c. 1964 - 1984, TMs (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Elliot, Angela - Elliot, George (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Elliot, William, 1985 - 1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Ellis, Craig, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Ellison, John [Broken Moon Press], 1991 - 1993, 5 TLS (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Ellithorpe, Paul, 1967 - 1976, TMs (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Elman, Dick, 1963 - 1981, Broadside (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Emanuel, James, 1996 Jan., 1 TLS (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Emilsen, William and Sue, 1989 Jan., 1 ALS (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Emmanuel Church, Boston, 1996 Apr., 1 TLS (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Emmerich, Karen, 1995, 3 TLS (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Engel, Kathy, 1978 - 1988, TMs (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - England, A., n.d., 1 ALS, 1 TM, 5 TMS (Box 34, Folder 19)